A Guide to the M. Caldwell Butler Papers 1945-2006
Lewis F. Powell, Jr. Archives, Washington and Lee University
- Impeachment of Richard M. Nixon 1973-1974, 15 cu. ft.
  - Printed Materials (Carton 49-53)
    - Congressional Documents
      - Presidential Campaign Activities of 1972: Legal Documents Relating to the Select Committee Hearings: Parts I-II. (Carton 52)
      - Presidential Campaign Activities of 1972: Watergate and Related Activities, Responsiveness Program (Carton 52)
      - Presidential Campaign Activities of 1972: Indexes to the Public Hearings. (Carton 52)
      - Presidential Campaign Activities of 1972: The Final Report. (Carton 52)
      - Presidential Campaign Activities of 1972: Indexes to the Public Hearings. (Carton 52)
    - Supplementary Material (Carton 53)
      - "The Offenses of Richard M. Nixon A Lawyers Guide for the People of the United States of America" Novemeber 1973 (Carton 53)
      - Brief on Behalf of the President of the United States July 19, 1974 (Carton 53)
      - In the Supreme Court of the United States "United States v. Richard M. Nixon" Nos. 73-1766 and 73-1834, (Bound) (Carton 53)
  - Memoirs and Oral History Projects (Carton 54)
    (Mooney, Woodlief & Hilton Head)
    - Transcripts & audiotapes: Mooney and Butler July 1974 (Carton 54-55)
      Box 55 contains audiotapetranscripts that are mostly duplicative of those found in box 54. The the contents of the two boxes are yet to be collated.
    - Impeachment Inquiry Project: A Digest of M. Caldwell Butler's Impeachment Reflections (Carton 54)
  - Printed Materials (Carton 56)
    Unlike the printed materials that are found throughout the Impeachment series, these books and magazines are not government documents. There are copies of Time, Newsweek, and Life magazines from the time of the impeachment. There are also books and a college thesis giving retropective views on that period.
- Bankruptcy Legislation 1972-1978, 18 cu. ft.
  The Bankruptcy Materials are 18 cu. ft. of papers documenting Butler's work in the drafting and passage of the legislation popularly known as the Bankruptcy Reform Act of 1978. Forms of materials present include: minutes of the Bankruptcy Commission, mark-up books on various versions of bankruptcy bills, memoranda, briefing materials, meetings transcripts, hearing transcripts, conference materials, Congressional Record Notebooks, audio tapes of mark-up sessions, and supplemental information on bankruptcy legislation with relevant testimony.
  This material was arranged by Butler's office into three major components: 1)general materials in ring-binder notebooks to which Roman Numerals were assigned; 2)"Supplemental Materials: ... " filed in "books" numbered 1-45; and, 3) Ken Klee's research materials. The arrangement of these materials is not easily grasped, but the donor has provided a "road map." A Butler document from around 1980 entitled "The Narrative History of the Bankruptcy Act Revision" provides a concise, informal legislative history of the Bankruptcy Reform Act of 1978 from Mr. Butler's perspective. It also discusses the creation and arrangement of these records and includes references to the Roman numeral numbering scheme employed by Butler's staff. This narrative is found in the first folder of the first box of bankruptcy materials(box 31). A second helpful narrative entitled "The Establishment of the Commission" states the reasons that impelled Congress to establish the Commission on Bankruptcy in June of 1970. This can be found in box 45 in the folder titled "Mun. 5." Ken Klee's article on bankruptcy legislative (box 46) may also be of use in understanding events leading up to the 1978 act. The article is entitled, "Congress and the Bankruptcy Act of 1976," and appeared in volume 61 of the American Bar Association Journal(October, 1975).
  The general materials have been removed from the ring-binders, but the folders that now hold them are labeled with the Roman numeral corresponding to the binder in which they were formerly housed. Everything from 1971 research materials to the printed public law version of the 1978 Bankruptcy Reform Act can be found here. Books and pamphlets printed by the Government Office of Printing are found in Roman numeral sections I and III-IX. Included here are the Commission on Bankruptcy Laws Report, H.R. 10792, H.R. 16643, Hearings on H.R. 31 and H.R. 32, Hearings on S. 235, S. 236, H.R. 6, and oversized side-by-side comparisons of VI (H) and XIII of H.R. 31 and 32 and S. 2266 and H.R. 8200 (stored in box 49).
  All of the "Supplemental Legislation and Testimony" is contained in 45 "books" and includes correspondence, notes and paste-ups of various sections of proposed versions of the bankruptcy bill. Section "F," of XLIII "Conference Materials" (Box 35, Folder 9 from the general materials described above) contains the index to the 45 books. Much of the contents are reiterations of information from the "Roman numeral" notebooks arranged for quick reference. Testimony is arranged by bill section.
  The Ken Klee's bankruptcy files were created while Klee served as associate counsel for the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights of the House Committee on the Judiciary. They are 4 cu. ft. in extent and are divided into three sections: uniform bankruptcy file, municipal bankruptcy file (MUN), and bankruptcy act subject files. An index to Klee's files is contained in Section "E" of XLIII "Conference Materials" (Box 35, Folder 9). The Uniform Bankruptcy Files are arranged numerically beginning with the number 102 and contain statements, testimonies, correspondence, memoranda, drafts and other relevant materials regarding the proposed bankruptcy rules. The Municipal Bankruptcy File is arranged numerically. The files are designated MUN with a corresponding number. These files also contain drafts, testimonies, statements, memorandums and reports. Klee's Bankruptcy Subject Files are arranged alphabetically. Included here (under 'g') is general correspondence from 1973-1978.
  - Subject Files and Research Materials
    - "Narrative History of the Bankruptcy Revision" (Carton 31)
    - Butler's Research and Documentation Notebooks
      #I - LII
      - Bankruptcy: Problems, Process, Reform by David T. Stanley & Marjorie Girth (Carton 31)
      - Minutes on the Commission on the Bankruptcy Laws of the United States (Carton 31)
        (A)
        March 19-June 14, 1971
        September 15,16-November 15, 1971
        December 13-January 30,31, 1972
        April 10-May 1, 1972
        June 12-September 11-12, 1972
        October 9-10, 1972
        November 13-14, 1972
        December 4-5, 1972
        (B)
        January 15-16, 1973
        February 22-24, 1973
        March 15-17, 1973
        April 12-14, 1973
        June 7-12, 1973
      - Commission on Bankruptcy Laws Report July 30, 1973 (Carton 31)
        (C)
      - H.R. 10792 October 9, 1973 (Carton 31)
      - H.R. 16643 September 12, 1974 (Carton 31)
      - Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights, House Judiciary Committee, Hearing H.R. 31 and 32 (Carton 31)
      - VI. Subcommittee on Civil and Constiutional Rights, House Judiciary Committee, Hearing on H.R. 31 and 32 (Carton 32)
        (E)
        (F)
        (G)
        (H) -- Side-by-Side of H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 (2 copies) September 2, 1975. In oversize carton 49.
      - Subcommittee on Improvements on Judiciary Machinery, Senate Judiciary Committee, Hearings, S. 235 and S. 236 (Carton 32)
      - Committee Print, H.R. November 18, 1976 (Carton 32)
      - H.R. 6 January 4, 1977 (Carton 32)
      - Amendment in the nature of a substitute to H.R. 6, (Drinian Substitute) March 21, 1977 (Carton 32)
      - Minutes of the Staff Meetings on Subcommittee Print November 6, 1976-February 25, 1977 (Carton 32)
      - Congressman Butler's Subcommittee mark-up book (Carton 32)
      - Memorandum for Members of the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights on Bankruptcy Issues (Carton 32)
      - Memorandum for Members of the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights on Bankruptcy Issues (Carton 33)
      - Minutes and Unofficial Transcripts of the House Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights of mark-up Sessions March 21-May 16, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - H.R. 7330 May 23, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Bankruptcy Court Draft May 16, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Constitutional Bankruptcy Courts, report by the Staff of the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional rights June 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights, Table of Derivation of H.R. 8200 July 1977 (Carton 33)
      - H.R. 8200 July 11, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Congressman Butler's briefing materials for the House Judiciary Committee mark-up sessions H.R. 8200 July 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Minutes and transcripts of the House Judiciary Committee mark-up sessions on H.R. 8200 July 14, 15, 19, and September 8, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - House Judiciary Committee Mark-Up Sessions on H.R. 8200 July 14, 15, 19, and September 8, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Memorandum containing tax related changes in H.R. 8200 September 6, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - H.R. 8200, Committee Print, Amendment in the nature of a substitute to H.R. 8200 September 8, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - H.R. 8200 September 8, 1977 (Carton 33)
      - Bankruptcy Law Revision, Report of the House committee on the Judiciary September 8, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - H.R. 9973 November 3, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - Description and Section by Section analysis to accompany Bankruptcy Tax Bill. Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights of the Committee of the Judiciary House of Representatives November 1977 (Carton 34)
      - S. 2266 October 31, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - Hearings, Subcommittee on Judiciary Machinery of the Senate Judiciary Committee November 50, 29, December, 1, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - Hearings before the House Committee on Rules on H.R. 8200 October 12, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - House Res. 826, (Providing for the consideration of H.R. 8200) October 12, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - Materials used by Congressman Butler during House floor consideration of H.R. 8200 (Carton 34)
      - Student loans Bankruptcy October 25, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - Harings-Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights of the House Judiciary Committee December 12, 13, 14, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - December Bankruptcy Hearings (Carton 34)
      - Bankruptcy Courts, Report of the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights of the Committee on the Judiciary House of Representatives December 12, 13, 14, 1977 (Carton 34)
      - H.R. 8200 February 8, 1978 (Carton 34)
      - Committee Print S. 2266 May 17, 1978 (Carton 34)
      - S. 2266 July 14, 1978 (Carton 34)
      - Report, Senate Judiciary Committee, Bankruptcy Reform Act of 1978, July 14, 1978 (Carton 34)
      - Side-bySide of S. 2266 and H.R. 8200 (Oversize 49)
      - Conference Materials (Carton 35)
      - Conference Materials September 1978 (Carton 35)
      - Bankruptcy Conference, Misc. Materials (Carton 35)
      - Bankruptcy Meetings, Unofficial Transcripts August 2, 1978 (Carton 35)
      - Deconcini Amendments September 23, 1978 (Carton 35)
      - Enrolled Bill on the subject of Bankruptcy (Carton 35)
      - Public Law 95-598 November 6, 1978 (Carton 35)
      - Congressman Butler's Subcommittee mark-up materials on Municipal Bankruptcy (Carton 35)
      - Congressman Butler's Full Committee mark-up materials on Municipal Bankruptcy (Carton 35)
      - Congressman Butler's materials used during House consideration of Municipal Bankruptcy (Carton 35)
    - Congressional Record Notebook (Carton 35?)
    - Supplement I: Legislative History relating to the creation of a Commission to study the Bankruptcy Laws of the United States (Carton 35?)
    - Constitutional Bankruptcy Courts: A Report for the Subcommittee on Civil & Constitutional Rights June 1977 (Carton 35?)
    - Supplemental Materials: Sections of Various Proposed Bankruptcy Legislation with Relevant Testimony
      - Book 1 - Book 7 Sections 101(1) - 341 (Carton 36?)
      - Book 8 - Book 14 Sections 342-507 (Carton 37)
      - Book 15 - Book 21 Sections 508 - 545 (Carton 38)
      - Book 22 - Book 50 Sections 546 - 752 (Carton 39)
      - Book 29 - Book 35 Sections 761-768; 901 - 946; 1101 - 1167 (Carton 40)
      - Book 36 - Book 43 Sections 1168 - 1330 Title II (151) - Title II (589; 771 - 774; 1477) (Carton 41)
      - Book 44 - Book 45 Title II (1478 - 1481; 1930; 244-254; IRC 47-1052) - Title IV (401 -411) (Carton 42)
    - Statements & Testimony May - September 1975 (Carton 42)
      Source 13 260;263
      Source 14 322-323
      Source 15 336
      Source 20 412-415
      Source 23A 502
      Source 50 549;554-555
      Source 30 587-588
      Source 31 595-596
      Source 33 612-613
    - Bankruptcy Mark-up Sessions, audio cassettes (Carton 48)
  - Ken Klee's Bankruptcy Files
    - Uniform Bankruptcy File
      - Preliminary Draft of proposed Bankruptcy Rules and Official Forms under Chapter XII of the Bankruptcy Act July 1973 (Carton 48)
      - Preliminary Draft of Proposed Bankruptcy Rules and Official Forms under Chapter VIII of the Bankruptcy Act April 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Tables of Bankruptcy Stats for fiscal year ending June 30, 1974 prepared April 1975 (Carton 48)
      - The American Bankruptcy Law Journal Spring 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Berkley Wright & Kent Pressan May 7, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Views of the Dallas Bar Association July 16, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Judge Joe lee July 10, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Tentative hearing schedule August 27, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Letter to Mr. Butler from Attys. Creel, Atwood & Spinuzzi, Dallas, Texas September 8, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Prof. Vern Countryman September 19 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Patrick A. Murphy; Statement of Peter F. Coogan September 25 (Carton 48)
      - Letter from Mississippi State Bar October 15, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of George M. Treister, Vice-Chairman of the National Bankruptcy Conference September 29, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement from the State Bar of California [October 13, 1975?] (Carton 48)
      - Business Lawyer Reprint: "Comments of Some Reorganization Provisions of the Pending Bankruptcy Bills," July 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Letter from the Law Office of Paxson, Smith, Boyd, Gilliam & Gouldman to Senator Harry F. Byrd November 18, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Business Lawyer Reprint: "Restraint and Reimbursement: The Secured Creditor in Reorganization and Arrangement Proceedings," November 1974 (Carton 48)
      - FTC Statement of David H. Williams, Atty. December 5, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Preliminary Draft of Proposed Bankruptcy Rules and Official Forms under Chapter IX of the Bankruptcy Act July 1974 (Carton 48)
      - Letter from Law Office of Hunter, Fox & Traube, Roanoke, to Mr. Butler December 9, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Harold Marsh, Esq., former chairman of the Commission on Bankruptcy Laws of the United States September 26, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Prof. Philip Schuchman, University of Connecticut Law School December 5, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Robert B. Morton, Esq., former chairman of the Commission on the Bankruptcy Laws of the United States September 26, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Linn K. Twinem on behalf of the Beneficial Finance System December 8, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Honorable Joe Lee, Bankruptcy Judge from Kentucky September 29, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Benhamin L. Zelenko, Esq. December 8, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of National Consumer Law Center, Inc. December 8, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Washington and Lee University Bankruptcy Conference October 13, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Clive W. Barre, National Bankruptcy Conference December 10, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - National Bankruptcy Conference: Bankruptcy Act of 1975, proposed draft (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Walter Ray Phillips on behalf of Household Finance Corporation December 15, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Testimony of Walter W. Vaughan on behalf of American Bankers Association and the Consumer Bankers Association December 15, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Beneficial Finance Corporation's listing in Standard and Poor's (Carton 48)
      - "The Bankers," by Martin Mayer, Chapter 13 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Rep. John N. Erlenborn January 29, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - Remarks of Rep. Ray Thorton January 29, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - Statement of the American Council on Education et al. January 29, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - Memo in regard to the testimony of Edward T. York, Jr. January 50, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - House Judiciary report of Proceedings: Mark-Up on H.R. 10624 November 11, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - House Judiciary Mark-Up of H.R. 10634 November 18, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Comments by George Ritner, Attorney from San Diego, re: H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 (Carton 48)
      - Comments by John Honsberger, Esq., Ontario (Carton 48)
      - "Is There a Way to Avoid Bankruptcy?" by George Ritner (Carton 48)
        Published by San Diego Urban League, Inc.
      - "Lucky 13 -- No Need to drown in a Sea of Debts," by George Ritner (Carton 48)
      - "The Bankruptcy (Chapter 13) Attorney -- Is His Role Expendable?" by George Ritner (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Attorneys Ward, Fernwood & Pederson, Oakland, California (Carton 48)
      - Statement of Hon. Joe Lee, Bankruptcy Judge, Eastern District of Kentucky (Carton 48)
      - George Ritner; Robert Ward; Andrew Leoni: A compilation with Index A to M (Carton 48)
      - Large black notebook of bankruptcy information 1975 (Carton 48)
        - -Recovery: How Fast & How Far?
        - Congressional Budget Office
        - Setting the Record Straight for a Comprehensive Revision of the Bankruptcy Act of 1988 by Judge Conrad
      - "The Tax Recommendations of the Commission on the Bankruptcy Laws Tax Procedures," by William T. Plumb, Jr., Harvard Law ReviewMay 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Kurt H. Nadelmann: The Bankruptcy Bills' Conflicts Provision: A Threat to the National Interest (Carton 48)
      - Supplement (Carton 48)
      - Stefan A. Riesenfeld: The Bankruptcy Bills' Conflicts Provision: A Step Towards International Harmony (Carton 48)
      - Kurt. H. Nadelmann: Statement on Section 4-103 of H.R. 31 (Carton 48)
      - Memorandum from Ken Klee on Hearings on Wage Earner Plans in Bankruptcy January 13, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - "44 Tips and Highlights -- for the attorney -- in Consumer Bankruptcy Cases," by Raeder Larson, Minneapolis (Carton 48)
      - Green Conference Briefing Book: H.R. 10624 (Carton 48)
      - Letter to Mr. Butler from Alvin B. Marks, Jr., Esq. December 15, 1975 (Carton 48)
      - Correspondence with Clauds kersey January 8, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - Correspondence with Ronald D. Stallings February 10, 1976 (Carton 48)
      - Letter to Mr. Butler from National Consumer Finance Association, Robert B. Norris (Carton 72)
      - Hon. Albert H. Quie Correspondence January 12, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - "Tenancy by the Entirety and Bankruptcy" (Carton 72)
      - Report on Provisions of Proposed Bankruptcy Act Relating to Community Property (Carton 72)
      - Tape and transcript of Mr. Butler and Mr. Parks, President of the Virginia Finance Association (Carton 72)
      - Minority Copy of the hearing and mark-up transcript February 5, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - John R. Butler Correspondence concerning H.R. 10624 February 10, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Letter from Vernon C. Loen, deputy assistant to the President, to Mr. Butler (Carton 72)
      - Memorandum from Ken Kleere: Bankruptcy Hearing on Wage Earner Plans February 27 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Clarissa Gilbert of the National Student Association on the Dischargeability of Educational Loans (Carton 72)
      - Witness List February 27, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Duncan H. Kester on behalf of the National Association of Chapter XIII Trustees with respect to H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 January 30, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List and statement of the Commercial Law League of America on H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 March 5, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List February 17, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - The America Bankruptcy Law Journal Winter, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Vern Countryman on H.R. 31 February 27, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List February 19, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Bankruptcy Administration in Canada, by John Honsberger (Carton 72)
      - "A Statistical Study of One Year of Federal Bankruptcy Cases in Massachusetts, with Emphasis on the Bankruptcy Bar and Examination of the Impact of Proposed Bankruptcy Acts," by Stephen N. Surbin and John Rugheimer (Carton 72)
      - Committee questions for James S. Parks and Paul L. Winkler February 23, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement on H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 by Conrad K. Cyr (Carton 72)
      - Witness List February 23, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of James S. Parks on behalf of Parks Finance Service, Inc. February 23, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Paul L. Winkler February 17, 1976
      - Witness List March 8, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Recommendations of the American Life Insurance Association (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Hon. Robert B. Morton, Bankruptcy Judge, District of Kansas March 8, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Letter to Rep. Don Edwards from National Association of Insurance Commissioners February 4, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List March 5, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Proposed text of the conference compromise of H.R. 10624, incorporating all of the agreements between the conferees March 9, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Response to Mr. Charles W. Hill, Director, Commonwealth of Virginia March 1, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of Alvin O. Wiese, Jr., on Consumer Bankruptcy and Statement of the National Association of Credit Management on the Purpose of Revisions of the Bankruptcy Act March 9, 1976; March 12, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 March 12, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Washington Post, "Going the Commuter Tax Route," by George Dawson and Thomas Muller March 13, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - N.Y. State Bar Association Committee on Business Law Report on Consumer Aspects of Proposed Amendments to the Bankruptcy Act (Carton 72)
      - H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 [March 12, 1976?] (Carton 72)
      - Letter from Hon. Robert B. Morton and statement of Martin S. Pinson March 9, 1976; March 14, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Final draft of H.R. 10624 March 18, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Letter from President Ford to Hon. John Rhodes re: H.R. 8532 March 16, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Need for amendment to S. Con. Res. 44 (Carton 72)
      - Suggested redrafting of Section 7-203 of the Bankruptcy Act by Patrick A. Murphy December 1975 (Carton 72)
      - S. Con. Res. 103, 94th Congress (Carton 72)
      - H.R. 31 and H.R. 32, Witness List March 18, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Letter of Franklin A. Cole and testimony April 7, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Hearings on H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 March 19, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Memorandum from Klee March 24, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List for H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 March 29, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Supplement to the testimony of William Rochelle March 29, 1978 (Carton 72)
      - Memorandum from Klee re: Tax Aspects of Bankruptcy April 2, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List on Hearings re: H.R. 31 and H.R.32 April 2, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Letter from Hon. Don Edwards, to Hon. David Alexander, Commissioner IRS March 16, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Witness List on Committee on Judiciary H.R. 31 and H.R. 32 April 5, 1976 (Carton 72)
      - Statement of A.S. Lawon, Assistant General Counsel of the United Steelworkers of America to the Committee of the Judiciary April 7, 1976 (Carton 72)